(Upbeat reggaeton music starts)
(Music continues)
Another night I don't sleep
Dreaming about that body
And that damn moment
That left me breathless
Baby, I know you like me
Don't play hard to get
Your body and mine
Make an unbeatable duo
An unforgettable dance
You and I on the street, eh-eh
One of those you don't forget
Even as time passes, eh-eh
Don't tell me no
I know you want to see me again
Baby, I don't forget you
Don't you forget me
Don't tell me no
I know you want to see me again
Baby, I don't forget you
Don't you forget me
(Music break)
(Lyrics resume)
And your dancing is an art
I want you to break me in two
Like a puzzle that fits
Your eyes tell me yes
Even if your mouth says no
That damn moment
When night turned to day
And you dancing with me
Without any rush
Don't tell me no
I know you want to see me again
Baby, I don't forget you
Don't you forget me
Don't tell me no
I know you want to see me again
Baby, I don't forget you
Don't you forget me
(Music fades out)